Indiana University President's Office Correspondence, 1913-1937 C286
Indiana University Archives
- Subject files, 1913-1937 (Box 1)
  - American University Union (Box 9)
    - 1919-1927 (Box 9)
    - 1929-1930 (Box 9)
  - American War Mothers, 1921-1934 (Box 9)
  - American Water Softener Co., 1926-1927 (Box 9)
  - American Wood Working Machine Co., undated (Box 9)
  - American Year Book, 1930-1935 (Box 9)
  - American Youth Commission, 1936-1937 (Box 9)
  - Amerine, Gladys, 1922 (Box 9)
  - Ames, 1923-1937 (Box 9)
  - Ames Emerich Company, 1916-1920 (Box 9)
  - Ames and Rollinson Company, 1915 (Box 9)
  - Ames, Goerge F., 1916 (Box 9)
  - Ames, Marian, 1919 (Box 9)
  - Amh-Amu, 1916-1922 (Box 9)
  - Amhurst College, 1913-1926 (Box 9)
  - Amick, Chester A. (Box 9)
    - 1914-1923 (Box 9)
    - 1925-1937 (Box 9)
  - Amick, C.T. (Box 9)
    - 1914-1923 (Box 9)
    - 1925-1929 (Box 9)
  - Amick, Esther, 1927-1936 (Box 9)
  - Amick, Helena G., 1924-1932 (Box 9)
  - Amick, John P., 1914-1923 (Box 9)
  - Amick, Louise May, 1929-1936 (Box 9)
  - Amidie, Terzo, 1925-1937 (Box 9)
  - Amidon, Lola Belle, 1934-1935 (Box 9)
  - Amiguet, Louis, 1925-1928 (Box 9)
  - Ammerman, Charles R. (Box 9)
    - 1920-1921 (Box 9)
    - 1924-1925 (Box 9)
    - 1926, 1931 (Box 9)
    - 1926-1927 (Box 9)
    - 1928 (Box 9)
    - 1929 (Box 9)
    - 1930 (Box 9)
    - 1931 (Box 9)
    - 1932 (Box 9)
    - 1934 (Box 10)
    - 1935 (Box 10)
    - 1936 (Box 10)
    - 1937 (Box 10)
  - Ammerman & McCall, 1922-1923 (Box 10)
  - Century Building, Indianapolis, Ind. 1933 (Box 10)
  - Century of ProgressLibrary Addition, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - Ammerman, J.W. (Box 10)
    - 1914 (Box 10)
    - 1917-1918 (Box 10)
  - Ammerman, K.V. (Box 10)
    - 1921 (Box 10)
    - 1926-1937 (Box 10)
  - Amnesty Committee of Chicago, 1919 (Box 10)
  - Amos, Anna Louise, 1931-1933 (Box 10)
  - Amos, Armon Julius, 1922 (Box 10)
  - Amos, Armin J., 1924-1934 (Box 10)
  - Amos, Dorothy, 1928 (Box 10)
  - Amos, Everett Grant (Box 10)
    - 1920-1921 (Box 10)
    - 1926 (Box 10)
  - Amos, Helen M., 1925-1935 (Box 10)
  - Amos, Henryetta, 1925-1928 (Box 10)
  - Amos Society Inc.,1927-1928 (Box 10)
  - Amplifying, 1931-1935 (Box 10)
  - Ampro Corporation, 1932-1935 (Box 10)
  - Amsinck, G. & Co., 1914 (Box 10)
  - Amsterdam, University of, 1930-1932 (Box 10)
  - Amstatz, Henry Clair, 1933-1936 (Box 10)
  - Amstatz, N.S., 1933-1934 (Box 10)
  - Amtorg Trading Corporation, 1929 (Box 10)
  - Automobile Blue Book Publishing Co., 1916 (Box 10)
  - An, 1913-1937 (Box 10)
  - Anastasoff, Tevetco, 1925-1930 (Box 10)
  - Anatomy, 1926-1936 (Box 10)
  - Anchor Packing Company, 1929-1930 (Box 10)
  - Anchor Supply Co., 1923 (Box 10)
  - Ancil, Katherine, 1922 (Box 10)
  - Ancil, Kathrynne, 1928 (Box 10)
  - Ancilla, Sister M., 1927-1928 (Box 10)
  - Ancient, 1926-1929 (Box 10)
  - Andel & Company, 1921-1936 (Box 10)
  - Anderson (Box 10)
    - 1913-1926 (Box 10)
    - 1927-1937 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, A.S., 1914 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Adrienne L., 1937 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Albert A., 1921 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Alice, 1927-1931 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Alice (Board of Trade building), 1915-1919 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Alice Elizabeth, 1930-1931 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Alice M. (Mae), 1923-1935 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Andrew C., 1915-1917 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Mrs. Arthur K., 1924-1930 (Box 10)
  - Anderson Banking Co., 1920-1931 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Beatrice, 1927-1932 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Ben R. (Rufus), 1921-1922 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Bertha Elliott Morton, 1920-1936 (Box 10)
  - Anderson Bible School and Seminary, 1926-1928 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Blanche Allan, 1924-1927 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Bonnie Ethelbert, 1914-1919 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Bruce F., 1915-1917 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Mrs. Bruce (Faustine), 1927 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Budd, 1934-1935 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, B.W., 1931-1932 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Carl, 1921-1934 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, C.C., 1930-1934 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Charles B. Jr., 1925-1927 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Chester, 1929-1931 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Clara Jane, 1936 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Clarence L., 1936-1937 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Clifton Oliver, 1926-1928 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Clover, 1925-1932 (Box 10)
  - Anderson College, 1929-1937 (Box 10)
  - Anderson College and Theological Seminary, 1930-1937 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Cora, 1918-1920 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, D., 1914 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, David Allen, 1921-1923 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Donald, 1927-1930 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Dorothy E., 1922-1931 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, E.G., 1915 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Mrs. E.H., 1917-1922 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Edna Fae, 1924-1929 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Edward, 1925-1926 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Edward A., 1914-1933 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Edwin, 1928-1932 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Effie L., 1926-1927 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Eli H., 1916 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Elizabeth, 1923 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Elizabeth, 1929 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Elizabeth J., 1925-1928 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Ellen Marie, 1936-1937 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Elsie, 1928-1937 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Emilie King, 1931-1933 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Emma R., 1914-1918 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Esther Luce, 1922-1932 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Eugene R., 1925 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Eva V., 1923-1929 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Farnum Shirkie, 1935 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, F. Lawrence Jr., 1937 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, F. R., 1934 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Faustine, 1923-1927 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Flora, 1918-1923 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Fred E., 1919-1920 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Fred L., 1917-1924 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Fred N., 1915-1924 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, George D., 1927-1936 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, George W., 1929-1936 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Georgia, 1930-1937 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Glen, 1916-1918 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Grace, 1923-1925 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Guy C., 1933-1936 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, H.H. (Hanson Hale), 1914-1937 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Hallie C., 1914-1923 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Harold Jr., 1924-1936 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Harriet Hayes, 1934-1935 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Harry Brutus, 1936-1937 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Helen M., 1922-1933 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Hendrick Christian, 1934 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Henry Oliver, 1928-1935 (Box 10)
  - The Anderson Herald, 1928-1929 (Box 10)
  - Anderson High School, 1920-1935 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Homer W., 1915-1927 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Hubert G., 1914-1927 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Indiana, 1916-1937 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Ira D., 1925-1933 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Iva E., 1918-1920 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, J.F., 1914-1919 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Mrs. J. Frank, 1926 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, J. Gilman, 1934-1936 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Jack, 1926 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, James A., 1933-1935 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Jean, 1914-1937 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Jesse Fay, 1916-1933 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, John, 1930 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, John Russell, 1934-1935 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Johnnie F., 1930-1932 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Josephine, 1919-1936 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Joy C., 1922-1936 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Kathryn Louise, 1925-1930 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, L. Grace (Leora), 1926-1937 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Laura, 1919-1927 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Lee Esther, 1928-1932 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Leota M., 1926-1931 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Lloyd, 1927-1936 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Loren, 1929-1933 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Lucille, 1924-1928 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Lural J., 1921-1926 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Mabel Naomi, 1934-1937 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Mae Mobley, 1930 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Marcialea, 1928-1930 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Marcile, 1931-1933 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Margaret, 1914-1936 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Margaret Marie, 1929-1934 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Marguerite H. (Hallam), 1924-1933 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Mary, 1930 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Mary Katherine, 1932-1936 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Mildred, 1929-1931 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Minnie, 1934 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Myrtle J., 1927-1937 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, N.J., 1930-1937 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Naomi, 1928-1932 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Nels, 1923 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Nola, 1931-1936 (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Oliver W., 1927 (Box 11)
  - The Anderson Press, 1924 (Box 11)
  - Anderson, Ralph J., 1923-1926 (Box 11)
  - Anderson, Ralph Jay, 1915-1916 (Box 11)
  - Anderson, Robert C., 1924 (Box 11)
  - Anderson, Robert V., 1919-1921 (Box 11)
  - Anderson, Roma Kathryn, 1924-1937 (Box 11)
  - Anderson Rotary Club, 1923-1930 (Box 11)
  - Anderson, Roy O., 1913-1934 (Box 11)
  - Anderson, Ruth C., 1924-1929 (Box 11)
  - Anderson, Ruth Elwood, 1932 (Box 11)
  - Anderson, Sue Grove, 1916 (Box 11)
  - Anderson, Thelma, 1936-1937 (Box 11)
  - Anderson, Thelma E., 1926-1928 (Box 11)
  - Anderson, Thomas J., 1930 (Box 11)
  - Anderson, Vera Grey, 1933-1937 (Box 11)
  - Anderson, Virginia, 1934 (Box 11)
  - Anderson, Walter C., 1923-1936 (Box 11)
  - Anderson, Wayne C., 1926-1929 (Box 11)
  - Anderson, Wendell, 1928-1934 (Box 11)
  - Anderson, W.H.G., 1913-1921 (Box 11)
  - Anderson, Bishop William F., 1915-1916 (Box 11)
  - Anderson, Zama (Harris), 1935 (Box 11)
  - Anders, Edythe, 1921-1928 (Box 11)
  - Anders, Gordon T., 1921-1922 (Box 11)
  - Andes, 1936-1937 (Box 11)
  - Andes Candies, 1937 (Box 11)
  - Andes, Irene M., 1915-1917 (Box 11)
  - Andes, Irene M, 1915-1917 (Box 11)
  - Andis, Thomas, 1933-1936 (Box 11)
  - Ando, Teresa F., 1929-1930 (Box 11)
  - Andover Newton Theological Seminary, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - Andres, Gragario M., 1928-1936 (Box 11)
  - Andres Stone and Marble Co., 1917 (Box 11)
  - Andress, E.H., 1925 (Box 11)
  - Andressohn, Johnm C., 1924-1933 (Box 11)
  - Andrew/Andrew(s), 1914-1937 (Box 11)
  - Andrew, Florence, 1916-1924 (Box 11)
  - Andrew, Francis Eugene, 1935-1936 (Box 11)
  - Andrew, J. Fred, 1913-1932 (Box 11)
  - Andrew, Margaret Inman, 1930 (Box 11)
  - A.H. Andrews Co. (Furniture Comp.) (Box 11)
    - 1914-1921 (Box 11)
    - 1923-1931 (Box 11)
  - Andrews, Alexander B., 1924 (Box 11)
  - Andrews, Berneth, 1921-1932 (Box 11)
  - Andrews, B.M., 1921 (Box 11)
  - Andrews, Edwin H., 1919-1927 (Box 11)
  - Andrews, Elizabeth Jones, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - Andrews, Elmer, 1914-1923 (Box 11)
  - Andrews, Fannie Fern, 1918 (Box 11)
  - Andrews, Ferne Rawlings, 1926-1930 (Box 11)
  - Andrews, Florence, 1920-1926 (Box 11)
  - Andrews, Frances, 1915-1927 (Box 11)
  - Andrews, Frank M., 1914-1937 (Box 11)
  - Andrews, Gertrude Freeburg, 1929-1930 (Box 11)
  - Andrews, Grace, 1922 (Box 11)
  - Andrews, Helen Hunt, 1917-1919 (Box 11)
  - Andrews, Hugh J., 1935-1937 (Box 11)
  - Andrews, Kate, 1919-1924 (Box 11)
  - Andrews, Leonard O., 1936-1937 (Box 11)
  - Andrews, Lena, 1920-1921 (Box 11)
  - Andrews, Mabel Dalton, 1929-1931 (Box 11)
  - Andrews, Nellie Rose, 1923-1932 (Box 11)
  - Andrews, Paul H., 1921 (Box 11)
  - Andrews, Raedel Marie, 1931 (Box 11)
  - Andrews, Ruth G., 1918-1924 (Box 11)
  - Andrews, William Jr., 1929 (Box 11)
  - Andrews, William H., 1929-1937 (Box 11)
  - Andrews, William H. Jr., 1934-1937 (Box 11)
  - Andrews, William Halstead Jr., 1931-1934 (Box 11)
  - Andrews, William Harvey, 1929-1936 (Box 11)
  - Andrewson, H.W., 1915-1924 (Box 11)
  - Andrick, Vera Delight, 1924 (Box 11)
  - Andry, Charles E., 1931-1932 (Box 11)
  - Andry, Paul, 1919 (Box 11)
  - Ang, 1923-1937 (Box 11)
  - Angell, George, 1918-1929 (Box 11)
  - Angell, James R., 1915-1928 (Box 11)
  - Angell, Norman, 1926-1933 (Box 11)
  - Angelo, Rocco, 1930 (Box 11)
  - Angle Steel Stool Company, 1937 (Box 11)
  - Anglemyer, Harold, 1936 (Box 11)
  - Anglers Company, 1914-1924 (Box 11)
  - Angleton, Joseph, 1932 (Box 11)
  - Anglin, Bernice, 1929-1932 (Box 11)
  - Anglin, Fred, 1924-1926 (Box 11)
  - Anglin, Opal, 1925-1927 (Box 11)
  - Anglo-American, 1926-1934 (Box 11)
  - Angola, Indiana, 1916; 1928-1937 (Box 11)
  - Angoli, Margaret, May 1936 (Box 11)
  - Angrick, Alma, 1926-1937 (Box 11)
  - Anibal, E.W., 1932 (Box 11)
  - Animal/Animals, 1920-1937 (Box 11)
  - Annan, Murray, 1926-1929 (Box 11)
  - Annear, R.B., 1927 (Box 11)
  - Anness, Milford, 1936-1937 (Box 11)
  - Anniversary (Silver) as President, 1927 (Box 11)
  - Annuities/Annuity, 1924-1936 (Box 11)
  - Annual Congress on Medical Education, Medical Licensure, and Hospitals, 1929-1937 (Box 11)
  - Anonymous (Box 11)
    - 1916-1926 (Box 11)
    - 1926-1930 (Box 11)
    - 1930-1938 (Box 11)
  - Anstett, Alice, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - AP (Box 11)
    - 1913-1922 (Box 11)
    - 1922-1930 (Box 11)
    - 1930-1935 (Box 11)
  - Apatow, J.J., 1933 (Box 11)
  - Apfelstadt, Gilbert, 1919 (Box 11)
  - Apon, Santiago, 1928 (Box 11)
  - Appelt, Edward Paul, 1927-1928 (Box 11)
  - Appelt, Ewald, 1925-1926 (Box 11)
  - Apple, Darwin Burton, 1930-1932 (Box 11)
  - Applegate, A.O., 1914 (Box 11)
  - Applegate, Elsie Louise, 1935-1937 (Box 11)
  - Applegate, Ernest R., 1925-1928 (Box 11)
  - Applegate, Jeannette, 1919-1921 (Box 11)
  - Applegate, Nora, 1915-1929 (Box 11)
  - Applegate, Nora Smith, 1930 (Box 11)
  - Applegate, Ralph, 1925-1928 (Box 11)
  - Applegate, Ruth, 1921-1931 (Box 11)
  - Applegate, Stephen, 1915-1916 (Box 11)
  - Applegarth, L.W., 1936 (Box 11)
  - Appleman, Cecil G., 1924-1929 (Box 11)
  - Appleman, H.M., 1918 (Box 11)
  - Appleman, Nina, 1928-1929 (Box 11)
  - Appleton, Allen M., 1924-1925 (Box 11)
  - Appleton, D.B., 1932-1936 (Box 11)
  - D. Appleton & Company, 1915-1937 (Box 12)
  - Appreciation League, 1914 (Box 12)
  - Appleton, Mrs. Mary Finney, 1936-1937 (Box 12)
  - Appraisals Corporation, the, 1929-1930 (Box 12)
  - AQ, 1922-1923 (Box 12)
  - Aquos Beverage Company, 1922 (Box 12)
  - Ara-Ard, 1913-1937 (Box 12)
  - Arata, Edward H., 1930-1934 (Box 12)
  - Arbaugh, Mrs. Charles (Irene Logan), 1924 (Box 12)
  - Arbitman, Oscar, 1935-1936 (Box 12)
  - Arbogast, J. Lynn, 1931-1934 (Box 12)
  - Arbogast, Paul B., 1927-1931 (Box 12)
  - Arbogast, Reba, 1927-1937 (Box 12)
  - Arbuckle, Elva, 1916-1918 (Box 12)
  - Arbuckle, Joy, 1919-1934 (Box 12)
  - Arbuckle, Russel L., 1924-1927 (Box 12)
  - Arbuckle, William W., 1929-1937 (Box 12)
  - Arburn, L.W., 1913-1937 (Box 12)
  - Arbutus, 1913-1919 (Box 12)
  - Arbutus, 1920-1925 (Box 12)
  - Arbutus, 1926-1932 (Box 12)
  - Arbutus, 1932-1937 (Box 12)
  - Arc-Arl, 1913-1937 (Box 12)
  - Arca, Alberto, 1920-1922 (Box 12)
  - Arch, Noble K., 1927-1933 (Box 12)
  - Archaeological Institute of America, 1914-1934 (Box 12)
  - Archbold, Florence, 1917-1925 (Box 12)
  - Archbold, Josephine Mildred, 1929-1933 (Box 12)
  - Archer, Dorothy, 1916-1921 (Box 12)
  - Archer, Fred, 1920-1936 (Box 12)
  - Archer, Lora, 1921 (Box 12)
  - Archer, Robert, 1930-1931 (Box 12)
  - Archibald, Sara, 1915 (Box 12)
  - Architect/Architects/Architectural, 1920-1935 (Box 12)
  - Architects- New Memorial Building (Box 12)
    - 1921-1922 (Box 12)
    - 1923 (Box 12)
  - Architectural Forum, 1925-1930 (Box 12)
  - Architectural Record, The, 1916-1936 (Box 12)
  - Arco Vacuum Corporation, 1930-1931 (Box 12)
  - Arc-Ray Electric Company, 1914-1915 (Box 12)
  - Arcus Ticket Co., 1925-1928 (Box 12)
  - Ardashier, Ruth T., 1923-1937 (Box 12)
  - Ardery, Helen, 1914-1921 (Box 12)
  - Ardman, Vivien G., 1928-1931 (Box 12)
  - Arduina, Sister Mary, 1931-1937 (Box 12)
  - Arend, Jessie Florence, 1914-1927 (Box 12)
  - Arend, Jewell E., 1918-1923 (Box 12)
  - Arend, L.J., 1919-1932 (Box 12)
  - Arens, Edward W., 1923-1928 (Box 12)
  - Areta, Robert, 1932-1934 (Box 12)
  - Arford, Clarice Izuma, 1935-1937 (Box 12)
  - Arganbright, Fay, 1924-1937 (Box 12)
  - Argus Pressclipping Bureau, 1927-1934 (Box 12)
  - Arisman, Ralph, 1929-1934 (Box 12)
  - Aristotle, 1932-1934 (Box 12)
  - Arithmatic/Arithmatical, 1923-1936 (Box 12)
  - Arizona, 1915-1934 (Box 12)
  - Arizona, Department of Public Instruction, 1922 (Box 12)
  - Arizona, Northern, State Teachers College, 1926-1927 (Box 12)
  - Arizona, State Board of Education, Phoenix, 1922-1932 (Box 12)
  - Arizona, State Teachers College, Tempe, 1927-1937 (Box 12)
  - Arizona, University of, 1914-1937 (Box 12)
  - Arkansas, 1923-1932 (Box 12)
  - Arkansas Department of Education, Little Rock, 1927-1929 (Box 12)
  - Arkansas State Agricultural School, (Arkansas Agricultural and Mechanical College), 1924-1937 (Box 12)
  - Arkansas State College, Jonesboro, 1934-1937 (Box 12)
  - Arkansas State Teachers College, 1929-1937 (Box 12)
  - Arkansas, University of, Fayetteville, 1914-1937 (Box 12)
  - Arkansas, University of, School of Medicine, Little Rock, 1929-1936 (Box 12)
  - Arkenberg, Evelyn Esther, 1925-1928 (Box 12)
  - Arkenberg, Hazel, 1927-1928 (Box 12)
  - A.R. Arken & Company, 1919 (Box 12)
  - Arkle, Joe G., 1931 (Box 12)
  - Arlington, M.E. Church, 1935-1936 (Box 12)
  - Arlook, Theodore D., 1928-1936 (Box 12)
  - Arlt, Gustav, 1923-1937 (Box 12)
  - Arm, 1921-1937 (Box 12)
  - Armand, Amy A., 1926-1928 (Box 12)
  - Armantrout, Dorotha, 1924-1929 (Box 12)
  - Armantrout, Luoise, 1923 (Box 12)
  - Armbruster, Frederick B., 1921-1930 (Box 12)
  - Armel, Clyde Stephen, 1934-1937 (Box 12)
  - Armenian Syrian Relief, 1917-1923 (Box 12)
  - Armentrout, Fred (Oscar), 1928-1931 (Box 12)
  - Armbruster, Juanita Hill, 1926 (Box 12)
  - Armfield, Esther, 1926-1935 (Box 12)
  - Armfield, Helen A., 1916-1917 (Box 12)
  - Armfield, Mary, 1919-1935 (Box 12)
  - Armfield, Thelma, 1931-1932 (Box 12)
  - Armington, Charles, 1926-1927 (Box 12)
  - Armistice Day, 1919-1937 (Box 12)
  - Armitage, Adelyn D., 1925-1931 (Box 12)
  - Armold, Ethel M., 1929 (Box 12)
  - Armory/Armories, 1929-1934 (Box 12)
  - Armour and Company, 1914-1936 (Box 12)
  - Armour Creameries, 1925 (Box 12)
  - Armour Institute of Technology, 1917-1937 (Box 12)
  - Arms, William S., 1929-1935 (Box 12)
  - Armstrong, A.B., 1925 (Box 12)
  - Armstrong, Beharold, 1923-1937 (Box 12)
  - Armstrong, Byron K., 1914-1935 (Box 12)
  - Armstrong, Charles F., 1928-1932 (Box 12)
  - Armstrong, Dorothy A., 1921-1935 (Box 12)
  - Armstrong, D.K., 1916 (Box 12)
  - Armstrong, Edward C., 1917 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, Ethel M., 1916-1918 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, Gabrielle, 1914-1918 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, George E. (Captain), 1918-1930 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, Harold, 1924-1927 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, Harold Smith, 1936 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, Helen, 1919-1926 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, Herman, 1915-1921 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, Irven, 1915-1936 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, James E., 1921-1924 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, Jessamine, 1914-1931 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, John C., 1926 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, John F., 1917-1937 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, Joyce, 1926-1930 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, Kent, 1928-1931 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, Laverne, 1928 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, Leland H., 1936-1937 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, Martha, 1923-1926 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, Martha D., 1915-1916 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, Martha E., 1923-1927 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, Mary, 1923-1927 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, Mary E., 1929-1930 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, Mary Louise (Miss), 1922-1923 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, Mrs. Mary Louise, 1933 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, Mildred B., 1930-1937 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, Muriel, 1936 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, Myrtle, 1913-1935 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, Orville R., 1929-1936 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, Paul Revere, 1922-1937 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, Robert, 1915 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, Robert D., 1913-1936 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, Roger, 1923-1930 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, Roland, 1926-1936 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, Ruby, 1920 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, Russell, 1931-1936 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, Ruth Louise, 1916-1937 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, Shirley (S.), 1916-1921 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, Thelma, 1925 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, Thomas W., 1919-1928 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, William H., 1916-1934 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, Winifred, 1923-1930 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong College, 1924-1927 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong Cork Company, 1924-1934 (Box 13)
  - Armstrong Transfer and Trucking Co., 1919-1920 (Box 13)
  - Armuth, Joesphine, 1936 (Box 13)
  - Army/Army and Navy, 1918-1937 (Box 13)
  - Army and Navy Co-Operative Company, 1922 (Box 13)
  - Army and Navy Journal, 1929-1936 (Box 13)
  - Army and Navy Register, 1921-1930 (Box 13)
  - Army and Navy Register, 1918 (Box 13)
  - Arn-Aro, 1913-1937 (Box 13)
  - Arndt, Dorothy, 1921-1926 (Box 13)
  - Arnett, A.W., undated (Box 13)
  - Arnett, Emmett W., 1913-1937 (Box 13)
  - Arnett, Trevor, 1920 (Box 13)
  - Arnette, Frida H., 1924-1925 (Box 13)
  - Arnkens, Conrad S., 1015-1937 (Box 13)
  - Arnold, Aaron, 1928-1930 (Box 13)
  - Arnold, Ann Elizabeth, 1926-1927 (Box 13)
  - Arnold, Arthur D., 1930-1931 (Box 13)
  - Arnold, Arthur Lee, 1933-1934 (Box 13)
  - Arnold, Constable and Company, 1932 (Box 13)
  - Arnold, Edna Ellena, 1935 (Box 13)
  - Arnold, Elizabeth, 1926-1927 (Box 13)
  - Arnold, Elsie, 1922-1925 (Box 13)
  - Arnold, Esther, 1923-1927 (Box 13)
  - Arnold, Florence G., 1914 (Box 13)
  - Arnold, George V., 1919-1923 (Box 13)
  - Arnold, Grace, 1928-1929 (Box 13)
  - Arnold, Harry, 1932 (Box 13)
  - Arnold, Helen Thomas, 1929-1935 (Box 13)
  - Arnold, Homer A., 1919-1927 (Box 13)
  - Arnold, Homer L., 1914-1924 (Box 13)
  - Arnold, Jean Margaret, 1934-1937 (Box 13)
  - Arnold, Jessie F., 1918-1924 (Box 13)
  - Arnold, Lewis Rhoades, 1925 (Box 13)
  - Arnold, Mrs, Charles E., 1929-1935 (Box 13)
  - Arnold, Pauline, 1933-1936 (Box 13)
  - Arnold, P.B., 1921 (Box 13)
  - Arnot, Eli Jacob, 1924-1936 (Box 13)
  - Arnot, John K., 1935-1937 (Box 13)
  - Arnsman, Betty, 1934-1937 (Box 13)
  - Aronoff, Joseph, 1936-1937 (Box 13)
  - Aronson, Eli, 1936 (Box 13)
  - Aronson, Harold, 1936 (Box 13)
  - Aronson, Harry, 1920-1922 (Box 13)
  - Arps, George F., 1916-1937 (Box 13)
  - Arr-Aru, 1913-1937 (Box 13)
  - Arrick, Byron D., 1923-1930 (Box 13)
  - Arsenol Technical Schools, 1927-1936 (Box 13)
  - Art Application Institute, 1929 (Box 13)
  - Art Metal Construction Co. (Box 13)
  - Artascos, Joseph Anthony, 1936 (Box 13)
  - Arterburn, Clay H., 1914-1919 (Box 13)
  - Arterburn, Lillian B., 1920-1926 (Box 13)
  - Arterburn, Lowell F., 1923-1935 (Box 13)
  - Arterburn, Norman F., 1921-1927 (Box 13)
  - Arterburn, Opal, 1922-1928 (Box 13)
  - Artero, Ed, 1925 (Box 13)
  - Artes, Nancy, 1936 (Box 13)
  - Arthur, Anna, 1914 (Box 13)
  - Arthur, Catherine, 1931-1934 (Box 13)
  - Arthur Clement L., 1932 (Box 13)
  - Arthur Damon E., 1932 (Box 13)
  - Arthur, Flo, 1923-1931 (Box 13)
  - Arthur, Grace Maude, 1931-1937 (Box 13)
  - Arthur Jordan Conservatory of Music, 1929-1932 (Box 13)
  - Arthur, Lee, 1926-1932 (Box 13)
  - Arthur, Paul H., 1932 (Box 13)
  - Arthur, Rev. E.A., 1925 (Box 13)
  - Arthur, Ruby Pearl, 1923-1926 (Box 13)
  - Artman, Clarence, 1914 (Box 13)
  - Artman, J.M., 1915-1922 (Box 13)
  - Artman, Judge Samuel R., 1923 (Box 13)
  - Artone Company, The, 1923-1924 (Box 13)
  - Arvin, Claude, 1918 (Box 13)
  - Arvin, Debourah M., 1924-1927 (Box 13)
  - Asb-Ase, 1914-1935 (Box 13)
  - Asbell, Clarine Sanders, 1936-1937 (Box 13)
  - Asbell, Ernest B., 1921-1928 (Box 13)
  - Asbell, Myrtle E., 1931-1937 (Box 13)
  - Asbury College, 1923-1937 (Box 13)
  - Asbury, Eunice, 1916-1930 (Box 13)
  - Asbury, Jenny, 1915-1918 (Box 13)
  - Asbury, Superintendent J.W., 1923-1929 (Box 13)
  - Asdell, Bernard, 1930-1933 (Box 13)
  - Asdell, Margaret, 1925-1930 (Box 13)
  - Ash-Ashe, 1913-1937 (Box 13)
  - Ash, Beatrice E., 11921-1927 (Box 13)
  - Ash, Elliott A., 1928-1930 (Box 13)
  - Ash, Ilo, 1923-1924 (Box 13)
  - Ash, Margaret Catherine, 1936-1937 (Box 13)
  - Ash, William J., 1934-1937 (Box 13)
  - Ashbaucher, Godfrey, 1920 (Box 13)
  - Ashbaucher, Hermina J., 1914-1921 (Box 13)
  - Ashbaucher, Lorin, 1920-1933 (Box 13)
  - Ashbaugh, Edwin, 1916-1920 (Box 13)
  - Ashbaugh, Ernest J., 1914-1937 (Box 13)
  - Ashbaugh, Frank E., 1934-1935 (Box 13)
  - Ashburn, Colonel P.M., 1920 (Box 13)
  - Ashby, Blanche, 1918-1924 (Box 13)
  - Ashby, Edith, 1928 (Box 13)
  - Ashby, Helen, 1915-1936 (Box 13)
  - Ashby, Ida M., 1933 (Box 13)
  - Ashby, J.R., 1923-1936 (Box 13)
  - Ashby, L.O., 1932-1937 (Box 13)